people already don't
have as much
connection as they
would like to
have. It's not
like this is
replacing some
sort of better
physical connection that
they would've otherwise
had. It's that
the average person
would like to
have 10 friends,
and they
have two
or three.
And there's
just more demand
to socialize than
what people are
able to do
given the current
construct.
And giving people
the ability to
be present with
people who are
in other places
physically just seems
like it will
unlock more.
If I have
glasses, it's not
going to make
it that I
spend less time
with my wife.
It's going to
make it so
that I spend
more time with
my sister who
lives across the
country.
And I think
that that's good,
and I think
people need that.
As for the
rest, I think
we could
probably spend a